The problem with
playing both sides of the
house is you're twice
as likely to get played.
Welcome to Live Eviction Night on Big
Brother.
Previously on Big Brother...
Thog's tyrannical tour of terror kicked
off.
I'm Renew HOH and I'm so excited.
And she sets sights on Taylor and Melody.
My name has been dragged through the mud.
I don't want to play any... I
feel like you know who you are.
But she also put her fellow tool shed ally
up as a pawn.
I have nominated you. Melody. Taylor and
Drew.
For weeks. Drew had been good with all
sides of the house.
The house is divided into two sides.
I've strategically
put myself right in the
middle and that's
exactly where I want to be.
Unbeknownst to him. Angela smelled a rat.
I can see that he's going to play both
sides because he has both.
Which quickly spread throughout the tool
shed.
You got a 22-year-old who's going to play
me.
I like Drew. but I think I want to get rid
of Drew.
So Drew went from pawn to target.
Are we in agreement that Drew is the
target?
Yes.
And even his closest ally learned of his
fate.
If Hayley was willing to cut loose one
pawn from the alliance. then what is going
to stop her from doing the exact same
thing to me?
With the veto vote. on
the line... Bottoms up.
Bottoms up.
Taylor drank her way to victory.
Turn up!
Look what Miss Taylor did. y'all.
Lyric made a pitch to work with Hayley and
her allies.
When I say I wouldn't
put you up and I'm not
coming for you. Chuck
and Kamal. I mean it.
But Hayley wasn't in sync with the singer.
I don't trust her.
She's going to jump ship like she did with
her other best friends.
And she made her feelings clear to the
tool shed.
It's going to have to be Lyric as my
nominee.
Kamu offered a different point of view on
Lyric.
My only pushback is that Lyric wants to
work with us.
Mallory has shown no interest in working
with us.
Therefore. I think that Mallory is more
dangerous than Lyric.
Which was anything but music to Hayley's
ears.
She has a crush on you and trusts you.
so that's a wash for me.
At the veto meeting... I have decided
to use the power of veto on myself.
The Hawaiian hoolid to the block.
Lyric. I'm not meeting you.
Tonight... Will the BB
Blockbuster be true?
Lyric or Melody's salvation?
And which one of them will be next sent
home?
Find out right now. live on Big Brother!
The tension is thicker than your hips.
my lady.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Good evening.
I'm Julie Chen Moonves.
Welcome to Big Brother.
It's day 31 inside the Big Brother house.
And head of household. Hayley.
has ruled with an iron fist.
Pulling no punches by weaponizing her HOH
to target both enemies and friends alike.
And at the center of her tyranny...
Hayley's ally Drew has suddenly gone from
pawn to prey.
And he hasn't a clue.
But the BB Blockbuster might upend
Hayley's plans.
Should Drew win. it's
Lyric or Melody who could
be facing the music
when eviction time arrives.
So. who will be the next house guest to
walk out the front door?
We'll all find out live tonight.
But first. the stage is set.
For the first major blindside of the
summer.
But is evicting Drew really the Tool
Shed's best move?
This veto meeting is adjourned.
I decide to name Lyric
as my replacement
nominee because she's
not part of the Tool Shed.
And so I wouldn't care if she actually
went home.
Drew is my target this week.
He has done a lot of bouncing from side to
side of the house.
And he's just really a wild card.
If Drew saves himself. Melody is my plan
B.
Melody doesn't have anything.
She doesn't play any game at all.
She's not nice.
And to be honest. if she went home.
I'm good with that.
You're fine. sissy.
Don't even worry.
I love you.
I knew I couldn't trust Haley.
But I was hoping that she would hold to
that promise.
Silly Lyric.
Naive Lyric.
Thinking she can trust people.
I just gotta go out and win that
blockbuster.
Bruh.
That was good.
Yeah. I don't feel great.
Obviously. Drew's my number one ally.
So. if he leaves. that's gonna be bad.
But I still feel like there's a chance.
There's a chance for me or Drew to win the
blockbuster.
In my perfect world. Lyric goes home.
That was iconic.
The Tool Shed has basically had it with
Drew.
And we have decided to blindside him this
week.
But I gotta remember that the Tool Shed is
ultimately a shield for my core people.
Devin. Angela. and myself.
So. whatever I do in this game really has
to be what's best for us three only.
Well done.
I tried.
I feel pretty good.
I got the Tool Shed in my corner.
And even if I don't win
the blockbuster. I'm really
hoping that they pull
through and keep me here.
If I don't win the blockbuster...
How are you with Lyric going though?
Bro. I'm super chill. dude.
Yeah.
I just want to make sure you're good.
Dude.
I care more about you being up there than
I'm there.
I'm sorry. Drew.
But the Tool Shed has decided that your
time is up in this game.
And it looks like you'll be getting a good
old-fashioned blindside this week.
However. I still have a final two with
Drew.
So if he stays. you better believe it's
business as usual.
I'm probably going to keep coming up to
you all week.
No. I can't.
And just say. like. you got me.
Yeah.
But I already trust you.
Yeah. of course.
I'm going to try to win the blockbuster.
but if things don't go my way...
Bro. you already know.
Yeah.
You boys better get out of my bag.
Hell yeah. brother.
Because I'd have yours.
I know.
Yeah. totally.
I've been trying to put on a strong face.
But. like. guys. I can't do it.
Like. I can't do it.
I need you to know that they made me throw
you under the bus.
This week. okay?
Mallory has consistently
said over this game
that she will put you.
Chuck. and Kamu up.
They asked me. is she going to put me up?
What is she saying?
And I'm like. it's not rocket science.
She would put you up if you put her on the
block.
And. like. Chuck. Kamu. and Hailey.
you guys are all working together.
So. yes.
Yeah.
So Lyric threw me under the bus a little
bit.
And she told Kamu. Chuck. and Hailey
that...
that I'm coming after them. which kind of
stresses me out a lot.
Because now they're coming after me.
If it comes down to Melody and Lyric.
I feel betrayed.
I'm going to have to rethink everything.
That was not fun having to frickin'
negotiate to make sure I'm safe.
Yeah. this whole time. I low-key.
like. want to punch Lyric in the face.
Like. I feel like such a person in this
place.
They're trying to turn me against you.
I. like... No. it's
not going to work.
Excuse me.
So if Hailey. Chuck. and
Kamu pulled through for
you. and. like. you weren't
on the block. like. what?
You would go work with them now?
Or what?
Let's go.
Chuck and Hailey.
Like. it's always been. and it's never
going to change.
If I stay this week. if I win the
blockbuster. we have to stay together.
Yeah.
Like. we have to lock in.
We need to fight.
Bitch. me and Mallory have been fighting.
We've been fighting this whole time.
I don't want to be here anymore.
What's up. Slick Devils?
What's up?
If the Tool Shed wants to get me out this
week...
I don't think you have anything to worry
about. buddy.
You don't think so?
I don't think so.
I'm a member of the Tool Shed.
You're kidding.
So. I think I would know.
Yeah.
Oh.
Well. look who it is.
What are you doing here?
You'll never guess.
I'm not going to feel. like. super secure
until Thursday.
After I get to compete.
We're going to be a support system.
We are blindsiding Drew. which sucks
because I need him in this game.
And as much as I want to
warn him about it. if he blabs
about it. then it'll be me on
the block next week as a pawn.
Scariest part would be if Melody won it
and I'm sitting up there with Lyric.
But then I'd have you four.
Yep.
Melody came off the block.
And then I'd have Mallory.
Yeah.
So it would be okay.
So you're good either way.
Yeah.
It looks like at this point. Drew.
if he doesn't win the Blockbuster.
is going out the door for an interview
with Julie.
I love Drew. but he's just been so messy.
he's become a liability.
I'll let you guys go
because I'm bad juju
and I'm trying to be
good juju for you guys.
That's a good term.
But on the other hand. like. I don't think
he'd ever put me on the block.
There is a little voice in my head going.
is this a good idea?
Love you guys.
Love you. buddy.
Up next. targets are questioned as the
icons rethink their strategy.
Then we head to the BB Blockbuster Arena.
Who will save their game
and which two will still
be nominees when the
live eviction vote begins?
Plus. the new guest panelist for this
week's BB Unlocked joins us live.
Who is it?
Stay with us.
We'll be right back.
It's time for America's Vote.
To pick which player you want to send
into the BB Time Capsule. go to cbs.
com slash bbvote and vote now.
A house guest can only be chosen once to
enter the BB Time Capsule.
Tune in on Sunday.
August 9th to find out the
next house guest to
enter the BB Time Capsule.
For online voting. go to cbs.com slash
bbvote.
Maximum 15 online votes are earnable per
person per day.
Votes will be accepted until August 7th.
2026 at 9 a.m.
Pacific Time.
Welcome back to Big Brother.
Drew's gameplay may be devilish. but sometimes
it's best to keep the devil you know.
What are you trying to do?
I don't want to go home.
Then don't.
I'm confused.
I'm trying to like play
it tough out there.
but this is definitely
the hardest week. man.
If I win this blockbuster. it almost seals
the fate of Melody. which sucks.
I get it.
It's hard.
She's kind of one of the people that I
like connected the most with.
She just reminds me of like people at
home.
So. Melody might be going home.
God. dude. it just breaks my heart.
I don't want to go home.
So. yeah.
Oh. hey.
What you guys up to?
I'm trying to talk about the benefits of
the two girls.
What do you think?
Um. I mean. I'm a little biased.
Thought you might be.
Yeah.
Like. genuinely.
Melody.
Yeah.
If she were to win. she's not going to
vote for you.
She's not?
No.
She hates Haley.
I swear.
I wouldn't be lying to you guys.
But obviously. I'm biased.
Of not but.
So. like. take that with a piece.
Bias. but also factual.
If I were you guys thinking
about who is more likely
to put me up. I genuinely
think. like. I swear to God.
They are going to put you guys up before
Melody.
And don't.
I. like. genuinely believe in the total
shit.
I've been on board with
taking Drew out of this
game because the dude
has been a little shady.
But the thing is. is he really a problem
for me?
Is he a problem for Devin or Angela?
He's kind of more of a problem for Chuck.
Kamu. and Haley.
And the thing is. don't we need that?
We need Drew to take shots at the red
corner.
We need the red corner to take shots at
Drew.
So. really. why are we getting rid of him?
Hear me out.
It's just an idea.
You can tell me anything.
What if we just keep Drew?
Bro. everyone's going to target him.
He's closer to you. me. like. and Angela
than them three.
This is a conversation I wanted to have
with you big time.
How would we go about it without burning
the red corner?
Or do we burn the red corner?
I think we can influence them.
I think we should keep him.
Drew is your competitor.
Who we can control.
I've been set on getting Drew out the
door.
But now Dee comes and says. you know.
maybe we ought to keep Drew.
Maybe he's actually good for our game.
And Dee's my number one.
Dee. one survivor.
Like. I trust Dee's intuition.
But what if there's a world where we talk
about weighing the options with Drew?
But how do we do that?
Yeah.
We have to figure it out.
We told her to put him up.
Yeah.
We told her he was the one that was the
danger.
Of course.
We have to make her now think that Melody
is the danger.
But I really think Drew is with us more
than he's with them.
They will put his ass up in a heartbeat.
They already did it.
Okay.
I agree.
He will believe that.
I do think this was a little wake-up call
for him.
They put you up.
And that would not have happened had Chuck
or Kamu said to do it.
Okay.
I see where you're going with this.
I like it.
I like it a lot.
I've been wanting to get Drew out for
weeks.
He's shady.
He's been playing in the middle.
I've been on to this guy since day one.
But now everyone sees him for who he is.
So if everyone's ready to get him out now.
we could get him out whenever we want.
We'd reveal ourselves really bad to Haley.
So what do you do about that?
Are you on board with the Drew thing?
So. the plus side of keeping him is he is
the snake that we all know in the house.
so he's always going to be a target of
some kind.
I think we can do it.
So. I'm down with the idea of possibly
keeping Drew. but if we do it.
we need to make sure that the rest of the
Tool Shed Alliance is on board.
And I think to do that and cover our
tracks. we need it to be their idea.
even though it's our idea.
We're discussing if it's the best thing.
Right.
Yeah.
We're kind of going over scenarios like
who to keep. pros and cons.
It is funny.
Of the three of them. the
one that would definitely not
put any of us up is the
one we're going to get rid of.
Do we still have our reservations about
Drew?
With Drew. it's like we
already know his game. and
quite honestly. I don't think
he wants to win an HOH.
I just don't.
Which is good for us.
There's more chances for us to win.
That's perfect.
Might as well just keep her or keep Lyric
and Drew and say goodbye to Melody.
because I know for a fact she probably
will not win it.
That makes such sense.
The only thing is there are going to be
physical competitions coming up soon.
and so Lyric would be the one to win it.
So basically where we're at is that Lyric.
we think at the very least all three
nominations would not be us. but she's the
most likely to win comps.
Drew. we don't know if he's even trying to
win comps.
And he's a little snaky. but would not put
any of us up.
And then Melody is the
least likely to win a comp.
but definitely all three
nominations would be us.
There are pros and cons to getting rid of
each of these three nominees. but it's
good to know that the Red Corner is at
least considering keeping Drew around.
It's looking more and more like this is
going to be a game-time decision.
So. America. I would get ready for Big
Brother's first ever live Tribal.
Up next is... It's the BB
Blockbuster Competition.
Three face off. but only one will win and
save their game.
Stay with us.
Every whisper. every argument.
every blindside in the making.
Catch them all on the Big Brother live
feeds on Paramount Plus and Pluto TV.
Welcome back to Big Brother.
Drew. Melody. and Lyric are about to battle
it out for safety in the BB Blockbuster.
And tonight. Paw Patrol is bringing us a
prehistoric blockbuster competition
inspired by their new movie hitting
theaters next week.
Before the blockbuster begins.
here's a special look of Paw Patrol.
the dino movie. where the pups go on an
exciting adventure to Dino Island with
their new friends. Rex. Timmy.
and Melody.
And Rhubarb.
Get ready.
Let's do this.
For the biggest adventure on the biggest
screen.
That one's Marshall.
He's my nephew's favorite.
It's got teamwork.
We've got to get the dinosaurs to safety.
Friendship.
I want a dinosaur BFF.
Heart.
You're the pup that never gives up.
I can do this.
And epic fun.
Stay cool. little doggies.
For the whole family.
This video is fire.
Like and subscribe.
Paw Patrol.
Only in theaters August 14th.
Rated PG.
Don't miss Paw Patrol. the dino movie.
only in theaters next week.
But the blockbuster competition begins
right now.
Drew got caught playing both sides of the
house.
Can he end up on the winning side of the
BB blockbuster?
Melody got caught talking
smack about head of household
Haley. but she can't
talk her way off the block.
And Lyric got caught selling out her
allies.
Will she have anyone in her corner should
she survive the night?
It's time to get the BB Blockbuster
started.
Hello nominees.
Hi Julie.
What's up?
It's time for the BB Blockbuster
competition.
The winner will immediately save their
game.
The other two will face off in the live
eviction vote.
This competition is called the Paw Patrol
Dino Puzzle.
Yes. we're talking about the Paw Patrol.
This competition is inspired by everyone's
favorite pups and their brand new movie.
Here's how it works.
On my go. you must race to complete a
dynamic two-layered Paw Patrol Dino Puzzle.
The bottom layer of the puzzle is a
landscape.
A landscape of Dino Island.
The top layer is made
up of the Paw Patrol
characters and their new
friends from the movie.
The first player to successfully
assemble their puzzle
and buzz in will win this
competition and their safety.
Does everyone understand?
Yes. Julie.
Excellent.
Then get ready.
Because this competition starts now.
Now.
What do we think?
Money?
Money or what?
Congratulations. Drew!
Won the BB Blockbuster. Drew.
And you are now officially off the block.
Yeah!
Good job. Drew!
I love Paw Patrol. baby.
Wow!
Great job.
So Drew is safe and
Melody and Lyric must now
face the others in
the live eviction vote.
And for the past 24 hours
the target has been in flux
so it is anyone's guess
who will be sent packing.
Stay with us.
Every whisper. every argument.
every blindside in the making.
Cash them all on the Big Brother live
feeds on Paramount Plus and Pluto TV.
Welcome back to Big Brother.
Let's head to the living
room and reveal the
winner of the BB
Blockbuster competition.
Hello houseguests.
You all know that Drew. Lyric and Melody
just competed in the BB Blockbuster.
And it's time to reveal who won and which
winner is the winner.
Which two of your housemates were made on
the block?
Nominees. head on down.
The winner of the BB Blockbuster is...
Drew!
That means Drew is safe from eviction
tonight.
Yes baby boy!
Baby boy!
Nice work buddy.
Congratulations baby.
Thank you.
It was a puzzle too.
You all right baby.
Shoutout Paw Patrol man.
Paw Patrol puzzle.
Paw Patrol?
Sponsored puzzle?
You know Paw Patrol?
Yeah Shot on like money.
I thought it was..
Of course the kick went through this one.
eh?
Get wild.
It was in Paramount Plus.
Excellent.
Drewski?
Four times.
No!
Oh no!
Oh my gosh!
It was like you hung this puzzle.
I know.
Good work.
All right. houseguests. please everyone
take a seat.
It's time for the live eviction voting to
begin.
Lyric. Melody. in just moments your housemates
will cast their votes to evict live.
But before they do. you
each have a final chance
to sway their votes
with one brief statement.
Lyric. you're up first.
Houseguests. I love you guys so much.
This has been truly the best month of my
life in here.
I've loved getting to know each one of you
individually.
It has been such an honor and such a
blessing for me.
If I'm good for your game. keep me here.
If not. you know what to do.
I love you guys so much.
I'm sending so much love to my family out
in Hawaii.
And aloha. Hawaii.
I love you guys so much.
Thank you. Lyric.
Melody.
Julie. you look gorgeous.
Houseguests...
I've had so much fun.
I've had so much fun on the show.
And I really hope I can stay longer.
I hope that my honesty in this game can
take me further than just this week.
I appreciate every one of you.
I'm so sorry. Julie.
I love you. Mom.
Thank you for the apology.
I believe we're on a delay.
But moving forward. houseguests...
No cursing. please.
All right. everyone.
It's now time for the live voting to
begin.
Haley. as current head of household.
you are not allowed to vote.
And as always. neither are the two
nominees.
One at a time. the rest of you will enter
the diary room and cast your vote to evict.
And tonight. since there are 11 of you
voting. it will take six votes to be evicted.
Barrett. you're up first.
Please go to the diary room.
Now that Barrett doesn't
have to blindside his
bestie. Drew. will he help
keep Drew's bestie. Melody?
Psst.
Hi. Barrett.
Oh. hey. Julie.
We have to keep meeting like this.
I know.
So what do you say you cast your vote to
evict?
Yes. I vote to evict Lyric.
Thank you.
Mom. Dad. love you.
Miss you.
Taylor won the power veto and removed
herself from the chopping block.
Who does she want to remove from the game
tonight?
Taylor. nicely done when you won that
veto.
Thank you. Miss Julie.
You're welcome.
Please cast your vote to evict.
I vote to evict Lyric.
Thank you.
Shout out to the field.
Happy first day of school.
Educators. Miss Scott. Dr. Fulton.
I love you.
Latrice managed to stay off the block by
throwing Melody under the bus.
Will she vote to throw her out the door as
well?
Lala.
Hello. my gorgeous sister from another
mister.
Please cast your vote to evict.
I. unfortunately. vote to evict Lyric.
Thank you. Latrice.
Thank you.
I love you. Madison
Barker. KJ. Lexi. Mommy.
Mr. Houston. Ernest. Aja
Lee. Rick and Auntie Linda.
Currently. the vote is three votes to
evict Lyric.
Zero votes to evict Melody.
The remaining votes. when we return.
stay with us.
Welcome back to Big Brother.
The house guests are currently voting to
evict either Lyric or Melody.
So far. it's three votes to evict Lyric.
Zero votes to evict Melody.
Let's continue with the live voting.
Drew shed tears at the possibility of
losing Melody.
Will he show his commitment to her?
With his vote.
Congratulations. Drew.
Thanks. Julie.
All right.
Please cast your vote to evict.
I vote to evict Lyric.
Thank you.
Love you. Mom.
That was for you. man.
Devens isn't aligned with either nominee.
So. what will he do?
Hi. Devens.
Hey. Julie.
Hi. Julie.
Please cast your vote to evict.
I vote to evict Lyric.
Thank you.
I love you. Becca. Jack. Juju.
Mom. Dad. Tony Kornheiser. R.M.
Mallory was stunned to hear that Lyric
threw her under the bus to the HOH Haley.
Will that betrayal seal her fate?
Hi. Mallory.
Hi. Julie.
Please cast your vote to evict.
I vote to evict Lyric.
Thank you.
Happy birthday. Sarah.
It's official.
With six votes to evict Lyric.
Lyric is going home tonight.
Well. let's see how the other votes fall.
Hi. Dee.
Hey. Julie.
Please cast your vote to evict.
I vote to evict Lyric.
Thank you.
Shout out to my girls at the crib.
Yennycel. make sure you answer my DMs.
because your girl's struggling in here.
Have a few dates lined up for me.
okay?
Bye.
Angela is notoriously wary of showmances.
Will she take this opportunity to shut
down the possibility?
Well. the possibility of Melody and Drew
becoming more than friends.
Hi. Angela.
Hi. Julie.
I'm playing till the wheels fall off.
I vote for Lyric to go home.
Family. I love you.
KJ and Sam. happy anniversary from Hailey
J.
She loves you.
Kamu has wanted to bring Lyric to his
side.
But did Hailey put a stop to that?
Hello. Mr. Kamu.
Hello. Mrs. Julie Chen Moonvesz.
How are you?
Well. thank you.
Please. cast your vote to evict.
I vote to evict Melody.
Thank you.
Thank you. John146.
Frankie Grande. tell your sister to hit me
up.
Shout out to CJMMA.
I love you. family.
Yash and Lyric have a final two.
but how real is it?
Hello. Yash.
Hey. Julie.
You look fresh.
Thank you.
Please. cast your vote to evict.
I vote to evict Melody.
Thank you.
Shout out Chipotle.
Chipotle is my life.
Chuck appears to be a bigger fan of Lyric
than Melody.
Will that hold true tonight?
Hello. Chuck.
Hey. Julie.
You look stunning today.
Thank you so much.
Please. cast your vote to evict.
I vote to evict Melody.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Shout out to my boys Greg. Jeremiah.
and Bellady.
Thank you.
All of the votes are in.
Looks like there will be a blindside tonight.
but it's not the one everyone expected.
Let's give the news to the houseguests.
Houseguests. the votes are in.
When I reveal the vote. the evicted
houseguest will have just a few moments to
say goodbye. gather her belongings.
and walk out the front door.
By a vote of eight to three. Lyric. you
are evicted from the Big Brother house.
It's okay.
I love you guys so much.
Thank you so much for the time of a
lifetime.
Um. good luck and win that money.
No. it's okay.
You're so fine.
I love you so much.
I love you.
I love you guys so much.
Love you so much.
Love you. Chuck.
Bye. guys.
Oh. bye. Drew.
Love you.
Love you guys so much.
It's okay.
I love you.
Win that money. guys.
I love you so much.
Love you.
Bye.
It's okay.
I love you guys so much.
I love you so much.
It's okay.
I love you guys so much.
I promise I'll see you all when I get out.
okay?
When you guys get out.
Love you guys.
Bye.
8-3.
Are you surprised?
No.
Why?
Not one bit.
I know that when you have someone who has
won competitions and someone who hasn't.
the competition player is
going home and I'm just so
grateful to have been here
and to have had this experience.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime thing.
So I'm just so grateful.
And I cry so much.
Do you know who the three were that voted
out Melody to try and keep you?
Maybe Mallory?
No.
Was it Chuck?
Was it Yash?
Chuck. yes.
Yash. yes.
Oh my God.
I don't know who the third one is.
Kamu?
Yes.
Why are you crying?
Because I knew that they would keep me
safe.
And I'm just so grateful to be here.
But I'm grateful to everyone
in that house because
they have been so
gracious to me and so kind.
And I'm just so excited to see my mom.
Like I can't wait to hear her voice right
now.
We saw you try and save
your game by going to Haley
and saying. Hey. listen. I
want to roll with you guys.
And you essentially threw your friends
Mallory and Melody under the bus.
100%.
Why?
I think in this game you
have to fight for yourself.
especially when your
back is up against the wall.
But...
I made a mistake to throw my friends
underneath the bus.
I thought that maybe it
could build some trust
with Haley and the
people she's working with.
I believe that there's a six person
alliance in that house.
Chuck. Haley and Kamu and also the reality
TV icons.
And so knowing that I tried to play into
that.
But I always knew that
if I lost that blockbuster
in the back of my head
that I'd be going home.
So totally fine.
You got that right.
But there's eight people.
There's also Barrett and Drew.
It's an eight person alliance.
I knew it because they were sitting in the
HOH room that night.
I knew it.
It seemed like you lost your footing once
Rome got evicted.
And you didn't know which way to go.
Had you stayed in one power. who would you
have targeted?
I probably would have targeted Drew and
Barrett.
Those were the people
that I said... Why?
Because I kind of knew they were in
alignment with them or at least like...
Why not go after the big guns?
One of the icons.
I thought that they would keep me safe.
I had a really good relationship with Dee.
But yeah.
In the event you were the one evicted. your
housemates taped some goodbye messages.
Let's watch and listen to some of them.
Okay.
Let's not cry.
Lyric. you are one of the sweetest people
I've ever met in my entire life.
I don't really know how this happened.
But I really truly wish
you the best and I
can't wait to talk to you
outside of the house.
Lyric. you are such a beautiful and bright
girl.
You're going to accomplish so many more
wonderful things in your life.
And I will miss you.
Lyric!
We are going to be friends outside of
this.
We're so sorry that it led to us evicting
you.
You were someone who was truly like a
light in the house.
I've never met someone who was so caring
and just always wanted to help.
We love you. Lyric.
I love you so much.
We'll see you soon.
Lyric. if you're seeing this. I really have
no idea what's going on in this house.
I think I'm in kind of a tough position in
this house now.
But I'm not mad at you for anything.
We'll always be best friends.
And hopefully I see you in October.
In the final seconds. we can't let you go
without talking about Rome.
You talked about marriage.
16 days in the house together.
Well. 16-day romance.
Is this the real deal?
It is the real deal.
I love Rome.
I can't wait to talk to him the minute I
get out of here.
Am I getting invited to the wedding?
Absolutely.
Is your father going to sing?
And what's he going to sing?
Nothing's going to change my love for you.
Lyric. thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
All right.
Have a seat.
I'm going to get us to commercial.
All right.
Tomorrow night. another episode of Big
Brother Unlocked is coming your way.
And along with Derek. Taylor. and Jerry
will be a special guest panelist.
I'll talk to them live when we return.
Stay with us.
Welcome
back to Big Brother.
He was the winner of
Big Brother 19 and just
came in fourth in Celebrity
Big Brother Mexico.
Please welcome back Josh Martinez.
Oh my gosh.
I had to.
You had to.
You know how to make an entrance.
Hello.
Hi guys.
Okay.
What do you make of this crazy summer
we're having?
Oh my god.
I love it.
They're all unhinged. unfiltered. and it's
kind of my style so I've been enjoying it.
It's been a good season.
Who would you align with if you were in
there?
I think a lot of people are
not going to find this as a
surprise because I did it on
my season with my brother. Paul.
I think it's probably my brother.
Paul.
I would align with the icons.
I think the icons are playing like true
legends.
I'm a big fan of Angela.
Love how unfiltered she's not in there to
win over fans.
She wants to win 750. so would work with
Angela.
And Dee's a good friend of mine.
So... Dee is a good friend.
Dee's a really good friend of mine.
So yeah. I would definitely team up with
her.
Okay.
And then it would be a bloodbath at the
end. but yeah.
I know you're going to delve into more
details about the season. but let's talk
about the difference between Big Brother
19 when you played.
That was nine years ago versus Celebrity
Big Brother Mexico.
Wild.
What was the big difference between the
two experiences?
I think the biggest blessing
I had. Julie. was getting
my start on Big Brother
because it was really intense.
I kind of grew up in there. which is wild.
But the biggest
difference was I didn't have
a fan base. like a Latin
American fan base.
A lot of these people
are icons. reality.
like not reality. but
like actors. actresses.
And I gained a whole new Latin American
audience and the public votes over there.
So kind of like our first season where the
public. it was a public vote.
So the public fell in love with my
craziness and they kept me till the end.
Did the public know you played and won
BB19 here?
Well. so they. I don't think they knew.
like that audience from La Casa de los
Famosos. they didn't know that too well.
but the best part was that our Big Brother
fan base. even though
some of them didn't
understand. they wrote
for me. they supported me.
So guys at home. I love you.
Thank you for making it possible because
it was a dream come true.
You're going to be on tomorrow night's BB
Unlocked.
I am.
What are you looking forward to most on
tomorrow night's episode?
I'm excited.
I hear that there's a very
iconic competition coming
back. which I'm so happy
that I'm going to be here for it.
And just Taylor and Derek are really good
friends.
Really. it's going to be fun
to catch up with them and
give my unfiltered thoughts
on everything this season.
The wall competition is what you're
talking about.
We're going to see that.
Josh Martinez. thank you.
Tune in tomorrow
night at 8. 7 central for
another packed episode
of Big Brother Unlocked.
Josh will join the panel along with Jason.
aka Selena. one week after being evicted.
And Lyric. who was just evicted moments
ago. will be there as well.
Plus. the winner of this week's BB Time
Capsule will be revealed.
And like Josh just said.
the classic HOH battle
of endurance. the
wall competition begins.
Then...
we're back again on
Sunday. Wednesday. and
Thursday at 8. 7 central
for more Big Brother.
And be sure to head to Paramount Plus
right now and sign up for the live feeds
to watch all of the summer's drama play
out 24-7.
For now. let's eavesdrop on the house
guests.
From outside the Big Brother house with
Josh Martinez. I'm Julie Chen-Bunvez.
Let's say it together.
Love one another.
Good night.
Sometimes the things you know and love
must evolve.
A new era of Survivor begins this fall.
Survivor. CBS Wednesday. September 23rd
and streaming on Paramount Plus.
Hey. it's Raina Baccarin.
A new season of Sheriff Country is coming
your way.
Action!
You won't want to miss a moment.
My mom is alive.
Sheriff Country returns part of CBS
Premier Week.
Catch up anytime on Paramount Plus.
www.aramountplus.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org